Guide to the Guerrilla TV Archive 1965-1997 MSS 138 MSS.138
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Files
  - TVTV The Good Times, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - TVTV Superbowl and the Oscars, ca. 1976-1984 (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - TVTV and the TVTV Show, 1972-1992 (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - TVTV Adland, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - University Community Video (folder 1 of 2), 1973-1995 (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - University Community Video (folder 2 of 2), 1977-1994 (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - Video Access Center NYU (also known as Alternate Media Center), 1973 (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Video Free America, 1972-1984 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Videofreex, Media bus, Lanesville, 1971-1988 (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Videotape Production Workshop, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - WGBH New Television Workshop, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - WNET and TV Lab, 1973-1981 (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Miscellaneous and Details: Display Selection, 1975-1996 (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - Miscellaneous and Details: early Guerrilla Video articles, 1970-1994 (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Miscellaneous and Details: Documentary Video History Notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Miscellaneous and Details: Guerrilla Television History, ca. 1984 (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Miscellaneous and Details: Video and TV Newspaper Articles, 1979-1986 (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - Miscellaneous and Details: Unlabeled Newspaper Articles, 1979-1991 (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - Cable and Public Access TV: Basic Cable, 1974-1982 (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Cable and Public Access TV, 1972-1990 (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Cable and Public Access TV: Public Access Study, Billie Mahoney, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Cable and Public Access TV: National Federation of Local Cable Programmers (NFLCP), 1977-1983 (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - Cable and Public Access TV: "Cable" Whiteside, The New Yorker, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Notes by Deirdre Boyle: Alternative Movements, undated (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Notes by Deirdre Boyle: Notes for Book, undated (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Notes by Deirdre Boyle: the Rise of Alternative TV, 1970-1983 (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Public TV and Independent Documentaries, 1969-1983 (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Public TV and Independent Documentaries: "The Independent Documentary: The Implications of Diversity" Conference Report, April 10-12 1983. (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Public TV and Independent Documentaries: The Independent Documentary Conference transcripts, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Public TV and Independent Documentaries: The Independent Documentary Conference, Journalistic Integrity Panel transcripts, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - Public TV and Independent Documentaries: The Independent Documentary Conference, Social and Political Documentary Panel transcripts, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Public TV and Independent Documentaries: The Independent Documentary Conference, The Broadcast Schedule: Diversity? Panel transcripts, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Public TV and Independent Documentaries: The Independent Documentary Conference, Options and Perspectives Panel transcripts and Corporation for Public Broadcasting remarks, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Public TV and Independent Documentaries: Patricia Zimmerman, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - Television: Mainstream Context, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - Television: History, 1954-1990 (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - Video Preservation, 1993-1996 (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - Video Preservation: Playback, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Video Preservation: "Let's Go to the Videotape" Workshop [organized by D. Boyle], 1993 (Box 6, Folder 183)
  - Video Preservation, 1983-1996 (Box 6, Folder 184)
  - Video Preservation: Media Alliance, MoMA, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 185)
  - Video Preservation: Schwartzberg Videotape Preservation, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 186)
  - Video Preservation: WGBH and the Universal Preservation Format, 1998- 1999 (Box 6, Folder 187)
- Series II: Videologs
  Written videologs and videographies for Documentary Video Classics and Subject to Change: Guerrilla Television Revisited. Videologs for Video Classics are located together at the beginning of the series followed by alphabetized videologs for Subject to Change.
  - Videologs and Videographies for Documentary Video Classics, 1969-1983 (Box 6, Folder 188)
  - Videologs A, 1979-1983 (Box 6, Folder 189)
  - Videologs B, 1974-1983 (Box 6, Folder 190)
  - Videologs C, 974-1983 (Box 6, Folder 191)
  - Videologs D, 1976-1983 (Box 6, Folder 192)
  - Videologs E, 1980-1982 (Box 6, Folder 193)
  - Videologs F, ca. 1981 (Box 6, Folder 194)
  - Videologs G, 1975-1983 (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - Videologs H, 1975-1982 (Box 6, Folder 196)
  - Videologs I, 1971-1976 (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Videologs J, 1978-1983 (Box 6, Folder 198)
  - Videologs K, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Videologs L, 1976-1983 (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - Videologs M, 1975-1981 (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - Videologs N, 1976-1982 (Box 6, Folder 202)
  - Videologs O, 1975-1983 (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - Videologs P, 1972-1983 (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - Videologs R, 1975-1979 (Box 6, Folder 205)
  - Videologs S, 1976-1983 (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Videologs T, 1977-1983 (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Videologs U, undated (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - Videologs V, 1973-1978 (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - Videologs W, 1976-1984 (Box 6, Folder 210)
  - Videologs Y, ca. 1977 (Box 6, Folder 211)
  - Videologs, Miscellaneous, 1974-1982 (Box 6, Folder 212)
- Series III: Notes
  Series III is comprised of notebooks, business cards, contact information and notecards.
  - Notebook, section 1, Pre-1965 (Box 6, Folder 213)
  - Notebook, section 2, 1965-1970 (Box 6, Folder 214)
  - Notebook, section 3, 1971-1975 (Box 6, Folder 215)
  - Notebook, section 4, 1976-1980 (Box 6, Folder 216)
  - Notebook, section 5, 1981-1985 (Box 6, Folder 217)
  - Notebook, section 6 Notes on Readings, undated (Box 6, Folder 218)
  - Notebook, section 7 Producers, undated (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - Notebook, section 8 Funders, 1970-1980 (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - Notebook, section 9 Organizational Notes and Outlines, undated (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - Notebook, section 10 Contact Information and Lists, undated (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - Notecards, undated (Box 6, Folder 223)
  - Notecards (color-coded), undated (Box 6, Folder 224)
  - Mini-notebook, undated (Box 6, Folder 225)
  - Business Cards labeled "Interviews(notes on reverse), 1981-1992 (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - Business Cards labeled "missing tapes"(notes on reverse), 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - Contacts A-E, undated (Box 6, Folder 228)
  - Contacts F-J, undated (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - Contacts K-N, undated (Box 6, Folder 230)
  - Contacts O-S, undated (Box 6, Folder 231)
  - Contacts T-Z, undated (Box 6, Folder 232)
- Series IV: Interview Transcripts
  Transcripts of some of the interviews conducted for Subject to Change: Guerrilla Television Revisited. Transcripts are organized alphabetically.
  - Wendy Apple, October 17, 1983. (Box 6, Folder 233)
  - Skip Blumberg, November 13, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 234)
  - Tom Borrup, June 17, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 235)
  - Ted Carpenter, May 23, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 236)
  - Jo Carson, January 27, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 237)
  - David Cort, November 9, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 238)
  - Blaine Dunlop, April 17, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 239)
  - Davidson Gigliotti, December 9, 1981. (Box 6, Folder 240)
  - Paul Goldsmith, October 13, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 241)
  - Mike Hazard, June 17, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 242)
  - Stephen Kulczycki, October 14, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 243)
  - David Loxton, April 2, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 244)
  - Ron McCoy, June 9, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 245)
  - Jim Mulligan and Greg Pratt, June 14, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 246)
  - Marty Newell, January 24, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 247)
  - Karen Ranucci, June 13, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 248)
  - Allen Rucker, undated (Box 6, Folder 249)
  - Kathy Seltzer, June 16, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 250)
  - Ira Schneider and Dena Crane, undated (Box 6, Folder 251)
  - Neil Seiling, June 17, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 252)
  - Philip Stack, October 3, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 253)
  - Ellen Soltes, undated (Box 6, Folder 254)
  - Parry Teasdale and Carol Vontobel, April 18, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 255)
  - Don West, May 21, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 256)
  - Megan Williams, October 18, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 257)
  - Howard Wise and Eric Trigg, undated (Box 6, Folder 258)
- Series V: Photographs
  Series V includes photographic images included in Subject to Change, video stills, and images from Video Classics. In addition to the four binders containing photographs are four folders of paper materials filed along with the images.
  - Notes filed amid photographs for Subject to Change. [corresponding photographs located in Box 7], undated (Box 6, Folder 259)
  - Articles filed along with Subject to Change photographs. [corresponding photographs located in box 7], 1979-1986 (Box 6, Folder 260)
  - Papers filed amid Video Stills [corresponding photographs located in boxes 8 and 9], undated (Box 6, Folder 261)
  - Articles filed amid photographs for Video Classics [corresponding photographs located in box 10], undated (Box 6, Folder 262)
  - Photographs used in Subject to Change: Guerrilla Television Revisited. Additional video stills and photographs located at the back of this binder., undated (Box 7, Folder data_value_missing_b0b66367a87d06ca365e71f511d40315)
  - Video Stills and Promotional Photographs, undated (Box 8, Folder data_value_missing_b0564880d1133006e0a9af5ae66b95ab)
  - Video Stills and Promotional Photographs, undated (Box 9, Folder data_value_missing_31cd64ce5bd3e88c503f7456fd8ea87f)
  - Video Classics Photographs, undated (Box 10, Folder data_value_missing_892cb094d0f250c61908c992f26d9347)
- Series VI: Catalogues and Brochures
  The catalogues and brochures contained in series VI are arranged in alphabetical order by sponsoring organization.
  - American Film Institute National Video Festival, 1981-1986 (Box 11, Folder 263)
  - Anthology Film Archives, Selected Video Works: 1970-1991 Michel Auder (Box 11, Folder 264)
  - Art Metropole Video Catalogue, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 265)
  - The Artists Television Network, Inc. SOHO TV., 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 266)
  - Ediciones Visuala Galerai, Santiago, Chile. Juan Downey: Video Porque Te Ve., 1987 (Box 11, Folder 267)
  - Electronic Arts Intermix., 1975, 1980-1982, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 268)
  - Independent Cinema Artists and Producers. Information packet and new releases., 1981 (Box 11, Folder 269)
  - Intercollegiate video clearinghouse, Inc. Video Library Listings., 1978 (Box 11, Folder 270)
  - International Center of Photography. Juan Downey: The Thinking Eye., 1987 (Box 11, Folder 271)
  - Joint Media Productions. Video Catalogue #1, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 272)
  - The Kitchen. Information packet and video listings., undated (Box 11, Folder 273)
  - Long Beach Museum of Art. California Video., 1980 (Box 11, Folder 274)
  - Long Beach Museum of Art. Video: A Retrospective 1974-1984 (Box 11, Folder 275)
  - MediaLog. Guide to TV, Film and Radio supported by the National Endowment for the Humanities., undated (Box 11, Folder 276)
  - Museum of Comtemporary Art, Los Angeles. The Arts for Television., 1987 (Box 11, Folder 277)
  - Museum of Modern Art. Bulletin for Film and Video Information, 1974-1977 (Box 11, Folder 278)
  - Museum of Modern Art. Circulating Video Library Catalogue., 1983 (Box 11, Folder 279)
  - Museum of Modern Art. New Video: Japan, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 280)
  - The Rockefeller Foundation Film, Video, Multimedia Fellowship Awards. Frames of Reference., 1988-1999 (Box 11, Folder 281)
  - The Video Data Bank Catalogue. On Art and Artists., 1983 (Box 11, Folder 282)
  - Video Inn Tape Catalogue., undated (Box 11, Folder 283)
  - Video Tape Network., undated (Box 11, Folder 284)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art. Biennial Exhibition., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 285)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art at Equitable Center. Video Art: Expanded Forms., 1988 (Box 11, Folder 286)
  - WNET-13. Independent Focus., 1983 (Box 11, Folder 287)
  - WNET-13. Independent Focus., 1984 (Box 11, Folder 288)
  - WNET-13. Matters of Life and Death., undated (Box 11, Folder 289)
  - WNET-13. Matters of Life and Death. Second season., undated (Box 11, Folder 290)
  - WNET-13. Videotape Catalogue., 1977 (Box 11, Folder 291)
- Series VII: Audio Recordings
  Interviews and conference proceedings recorded on audiocassette.
  - Subseries A: Guerrilla TV Interviews
    - Peter Adair, San Francisco, Film to video crossover, some stories, new tape, 09/30/1983; 138.0001 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0001, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0001)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD 90, Duration: 75 min.
    - Lynn Adler, San Francisco, Founder of Optic Nerve, discussion on organization and Fifty Wonderful Years, 10/3/1983; 138.0002 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0002, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0002)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 94 min.
      Scope and Content
      Program Content: Unknown
    - Louis Alvarez and Andy Kolker, New Orleans, New Center for Media. Discusses New Orleans Video Access Center (NOVAC), departure and the founding of the New Center for Media. Part 1 of 3, 1/30/1984, 1/31/1984; 138.0003 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0003, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0003)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, 92 min.
    - Louis Alvarez and Andy Kolker, New Orleans, New Center for Media. Discusses NOVAC, departure and the founding of the New Center for Media. Part 2 of 3, 1/31/1984; 138.0004 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0004, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0003)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 95 min.
    - Louis Alvarez and Andy Kolker, New Orleans, New Center for Media. Discusses NOVAC, departure and the founding of the New Center for Media. Part 3 of 3, 1/30/1984, 1/31/1984; 138.0005 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0005, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0005)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 48 min.
    - Elle Anthony, St. Cloud Minnesota, "Dairy Queens" and "Stay With Me", 6/15/1983; 138.0006 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0006, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0006)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK SA90, Duration: 52 min.
    - Wendy Apple, Topanga Canyon, discusses TVTV, Cable entrep work, women's roles, personalities. Part 1 of 2, 10/17/1983; 138.0007 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0007, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0007)
    - Wendy Apple, Topanga Canyon, discusses TVTV, Cable entrep work, women's roles, personalities. Part 2 of 2, 10/17/1983; 138.0008 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0008, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0008)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 55 min.
    - Fred Barzyck, Boston, discusses WGBH. Part 1 of 2., 11/7/1983; 138.0009 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0009, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0009)
    - Fred Barzyck, Boston, discusses WGBH. Part 2 of 2, 11/7/1983; 138.0010 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0010, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0010)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 10 min.
    - Dara Birnbaum. Part 1 of 2, 12/17/1981; 138.0011 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0011, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0011)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, Duration: 65 min.
    - Dara Birnbaum. Part 2 of 2, 12/17/1981; 138.0012 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0012, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0012)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, Duration: 32 min.
    - Richard Blaustein, Johnson City TN, ETSU, discusses SAVES an Appalachian ethnographic series., 1/27/1984; 138.0013 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0013, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0013)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 13 min.
    - Skip Blumberg, TVTV, discusses "Pick Up Your Feet" Part 1 of 2, 11/13/1981; 138.0014 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0014, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0014)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell UD90, Duration: 95 min.
    - Skip Blumberg, TVTV, discusses "Pick Up Your Feet" Part 2 of 2, 11/13/1981; 138.0015 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0015, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0015)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Lafayette criterion 60, Duration: 63 min.
    - Skip Blumberg, TVTV, discusses "Eskimo Olympics" and early video days. Part 1 of 3, 4/22/1983; 138.0016 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0016, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0016)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, Duration: 64 min.
    - Skip Blumberg, TVTV, discusses "Eskimo Olympics" and early video days. Part 2 of 3, 4/22/1983; 138.0017 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0017, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0017)
    - Skip Blumberg, TVTV, discusses "Eskimo Olympics" and early video days. Part 3 of 3, 4/22/1983; 138.0018 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0018, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0018)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, Duration: 19 min.
    - Tom Borrup, Minneapolis, Director of UCV., 6/17/1983; 138.0019 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0019, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0019)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK SA90, Duration: 77 min.
    - Peter Bradley, Minneapolis, Discussing NYSCA and the founding of video., 6/16/1983; 138.0020 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0020, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0020)
    - Carol Brandenburg, WNET TV Lab., 4/18/1984; 138.0021 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0021, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0021)
    - Broadside TV's First Board Meeting, 1975; 138.0022 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0022, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0022)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C90, Duration: 58 min.
    - David Brown, discussing UCV., 5/17/1983; 138.0023 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0023, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0023)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Scotch BX90, Duration: 65 min.
    - Nancy Cain, 3/8/1992; 138.0024 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0024, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0024)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK D90, Duration: 95 min.
    - Tobe Carey, Woodstock NY, Discusses early work, Woodstock Community Video and Willow media, 2/24/1984; 138.0025 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0025, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0024)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C90, Duration: 54 min.
    - Ted Carpenter, Silver Springs MD, Discusses founding of Broadside TV, 5/23/1984; 138.0026 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0026, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0026)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, Duration: 85 min.
    - Jo Carson, Johnson City TN, Discusses Broadside TV and Impact on her life, 1/27/1984; 138.0027 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0027, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0027)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 30 min.
    - Tom Christy, Johnson City TN, Discusses Broadside TV, 1/26/1984; 138.0028 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0028, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0028)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 34 min.
    - Maxi Cohen, New York, Discusses Video Access Center and Video Repertory. Part 1 of 2, 3/30/1984; 138.0029 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0029, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0029)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell UD90, Duration: 93 min.
    - Maxi Cohen, New York, Discusses Video Access Center and Video Repertory. Part 2 of 2, 3/30/1984; 138.0030 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0030, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0030)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, Duration: 64 min.
    - Vicki Costello, Los Angeles, Discusses early days of Washington Community Video, TVs, Family, Feminist shift Part 1 of 2, 10/14/1983; 138.0031 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0031, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0031)
    - Vicki Costello, Los Angeles, Discusses early days of Washington Community Video, TVs, Family and Feminist shift, Part 2 of 2, 10/14/1983; 138.0032 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0032, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0032)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 19 min.
    - David Cort, Boston, Discusses Videofreex and Lanesville TV. 1 of 2, 11/9/1983; 138.0033 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0033, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0033)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90
    - David Cort, Boston, discusses Videofreex and Lanesville TV. 2 of 2, 11/9/1983; 138.0034 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0034, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0034)
    - Peter D'Agostino, 11/23/1981; 138.0035 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0035, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0035)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C90, Duration: 64 min.
    - Jim Day, Public TV, 10/24/1984; 138.0036 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0036, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0036)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Scotch BX90, Duration: 82 min.
    - Nick DeMartino, Washington DC, 12/14/1981; 138.0037 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0037, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0037)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, Duration: 58 min.
    - Nick DeMartino, discusses Washington Community Video, Public Interest Video Network, Carnegie Commission, the public trust and keeping pace with new TV. 1 of 2, 5/23/1984; 138.0038 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0038, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0038)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony CHF90, Duration: 95 min.
    - Nick DeMartino, discusses Washington Community Video, Public Interest Video Network, Carnegie Commission, the public trust and keeping pace with new TV. 2 of 2, 5/23/1984; 138.0039 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0039, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0039)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony CHF90, Duration: 28 min.
    - Janet Densmore, New Orleans "Algiers Incident"., 2/3/1984; 138.0040 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0040, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0040)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 78 min.
    - Blaine Dunlop, Atlanta, discusses Broadside TV and collaboration with Sol Korine., 4/17/1983; 138.0041 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0041, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0041)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK SA90, Duration: 94 min.
    - Bonnie Engel, San Francisco, Founder of Mobius Video Festival, 10/8/1983; 138.0042 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0042, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0042)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 83 min.
    - Mary Esbjornson, New York, discusses UCV and Intermedia Arts., undated; 138.0043 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0043, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0043)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, JVC GI-90, Duration: 77 min.
    - Kit Fitzgerald and John Sanborn. Part 1 of 2, 12/19/1981; 138.0044 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0044, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0044)
    - Kit Fitzgerald and John Sanborn. Part 2 of 2, 12/19/1981; 138.0045 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0045, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0045)
    - Davidson Gigliotti. Part 1 of 2, 12/9/1981; 138.0046 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0046, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0046)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, Duration: 67 min.
    - Side one: Davidson Gigliotti, Side two: Kitty Morgan. Part 2 of 2, 12/9/1981; 138.0047 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0047, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0047)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, Duration: 57 min.
    - Sharon Goldenberg, Encino CA, discusses feminist video in Vermont, now in cable, 10/13/1983; 138.0048 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0048, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0048)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 65 min.
    - Paul Goldsmith, Los Angeles, disccusses TVTV genres, 10/13/1983; 138.0049 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0049, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0049)
    - Shalom Gorewitz, 12/15/1981; 138.0050 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0050, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0050)